Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hi. my name is Peter Parker.
You don't remember me. but I have
something to tell you
that's gonna sound crazy.
But it's the truth.
And I know you're gonna believe me
because you're very good
at telling when I'm lying.
E.V.. can you check the
calibration of my targeting matrix?
That doesn't feel zeroed into me.
Checking target calibration.
Hey E.V.. take five.
Standing by.
We used to know each other.
We were together. but
something bad was gonna happen.
And the only way to stop it
was to make everyone forget me.
First day at MIT. let's go!
My gosh. we're here. we made it!
MJ. come on.
Including you.
Pretend like you're not the happiest
you've ever been in
your entire life right now.
I can't.
You just did it!
Okay. okay. okay.
I'm gonna be hugging!
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
I'm really. really
understanding the culture out here
of Boston. it's just so different.
And sometimes Spider-Man
has to do the hard thing
even if it breaks Peter Parker's heart.
When everyone hears like.
"Pahk the cah by the hahba"
And maybe that's my responsibility.
To live alone with the truth.
But the truth is. MJ. that I love you.
And I hope that deep
down. something inside of you
remembers that you love me too.
Suspect is 5'8". 5'10". medium build.
But until then. I'm
just gonna be Spider-Man.
Incoming!
Hey. hey. hey. whoa. whoa. whoa!
Members of the Manfredi crime syndicate
were apprehended by Spider-Man yesterday.
Hey. we live on the same floor.
Cool.
Does anybody ever come up here?
Not unless they like asbestos.
We've just been using it for storage.
It's perfect.
Hey. everyone. sophomore-year-Ned is back.
Older. wiser. flier. ha-ha. let's go!
Whoa.
What?
He's on your face.
How do you feel about it?
I mean. you look like an assistant coach.
You sure you wanna do this. Scorpion?
Did you miss me. Spidey?
If I drop you from here.
how long do you think it
would take you to hit the ground?
I don't know. you tell me.
Let's end this on a high note?
Yo. Lonnie. what happened?
DeWolff. all the
evidence you're gonna need
is in the trunk of his car.
You trying to take my job. Spider-Man?
Hey. you guys are the professionals.
I'm just the volunteer.
It's a new New York.
Thanks to Spider-Man.
crime rates have dropped
to a record low.
Police and damage
control give much of the credit
to the masked hero.
Initiate HUD tests.
Armed robbery at Civic Union Bank.
In the past six months. he has taken down
every major crime lord
across the five boroughs.
including the
super-powered ninja group. The Hand.
He is the pride of New York City.
the hero every grown-up relies on
and every kid wants to be.
Final semester. MIT.
My gosh. we're graduating in a month.
We've made so many memories.
Where do I begin?
Night swimming in the
Charles River with Jim and Wylie.
the infamous food
fight at the Banana Lounge.
pulling all-nighters in stud
five with MJ and Nate Dawg.
It feels like yesterday
I was sitting on a roof
with MJ dreaming
about coming here together
and I still can't believe we did it.
I'm so grateful for all
the friends that I've made.
I couldn't imagine going
through this with anyone else.
Ned. who do you think is actually watching these?
I don't know. maybe someone.
Okay. well. bye someone.
What? Bye. we're done.
No!
I mean. we're talking
about downtown Brooklyn
in broad daylight.
High profile job like that.
you know that Foswell was involved.
Yeah. I hear you. but can you prove it?
Yeah. I'm going
through his financial records
and I'm following his crew every night.
Do you do anything besides work?
You know the saying.
you do something you love.
you don't work a day in your life.
Can't be in that.
Mom. where's my calculator?
I don't know.
Trust me. all right?
Being married to the job never ends well.
Don't worry about it. I'll be okay.
Yeah?
You still getting them headaches though?
Yeah. but I'll be fine.
I don't know. man.
I think your body's
trying to tell you something.
Like you need to get out of that suit
every once in a while.
Mom. do you know where my calculator is?
I don't know. papi.
What you need is some
real human connection.
What. and we're not connecting?
Nah. dude.
I don't know your name. your
face. or nothing about you.
I don't think you've ever asked me
a question about my life.
Sure I have.
Yeah. what are my kids' names?
Well. for starters.
your son's name's Poppy.
Is it Spider-Man?
I can't tell you that. sweetheart.
That means it's Spider-Man?
Gosh.
A hijacked tank is heading
southbound past 34th Street.
All available units respond.
Hey. you getting this?
More work. lucky you.
Okay. I'll see you out there.
I'm so sorry. I gotta go.
Whoa!
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
I got you. Spidey!
No. no. I don't need you.
Hey. head up!
You okay. kid?
Yeah. you're okay.
See you later.
You wouldn't know it
just by looking at it.
but this very street
was completely destroyed
in the Battle of New York.
Come on. come on!
God!
Come on.
What the hell. Frank?
You just hit me with a van!
Quit your whimpering.
We're not doing that again. Frank.
You're goddamn right we're not.
This time you're gonna
get the hell out of my way.
What. you mean
instead of saving your life?
Nah. you gotta talk
about that Staten Island
bullshit again?
Nah. well you said it. not me.
It is.
Look. man. you can't just shoot yourself
out of every situation.
Innocent people get hurt.
What do you think's
downrange in that tank. dumb-dumb?
Suit yourself.
Jackass.
This frickin' guy.
Mother.....
Go home. Frank.
I'm gonna kill this kid.
DeWolff? -Are you gonna
stop that thing or what?
Heading straight for the damage control
detention center.
I'm trying.
Try harder. there's a lot of scary dudes
locked up in there.
Who do you think put them in there?
Let's go. scorpion.
Moving day.
Come on.
Freeze. leave us now.
All right. everybody clear out.
This guy is armed and dangerous.
Get out of the vehicle. ma'am.
I was thinking the same thing.
Spider-Man?
Where am I?
What the?
Keep her for questioning. Clear the building.
Enjoy the ride. scorpion.
You won't be seeing
much daylight in Supermax.
Scorpions are nocturnal. buddy.
The building is under attack.
Get the prisoner out of here now.
Sir!
You gotta take off now.
The building isn't breached. go. go.
All right. fire up. go. go.
Change of plans!
Take him to the helipad at Bellevue.
What?
That's an order from the
Director Metzger. go. now!
Copy that.
Hey. what?
How did I get up here?
Spider-Man. save me. would you?
Who are you?
You can see me.
Tell me who you are.
You first.
Hey. name.
You pushed me out. interesting.
What the hell was that?
Did you just try to jump into my mind?
You know. the whole time
you've been chasing me.
you forgot to ask yourself
a very important question.
What's in the tank?
Go!
Spider-Man?
What just happened?
I don't know.
Hey. way to go. Spidey. You guys okay? You good?
I swear. all the things I said I did.
I don't remember doing anything.
It's okay. it's okay. look.
let these people take good care of you.
I would never hurt you.
I love you. Spider-Man.
Yeah. all right. buddy. all right.
Hey. what do you got?
Here. get this.
Chopper took Scorpion to Bellevue.
10 minutes later. a guard
walked him right out the door.
What?
What about the tank?
Stolen from the damage
control warehouse in Brooklyn.
driver was a janitor who worked there.
You got a motive?
Nada. And no criminal record.
Scorpion must've gotten to her somehow.
Yeah. maybe.
What do you mean maybe?
I mean. I don't know.
but I know someone that might.
Where you going?
You keep following the leads on Scorpion.
I'm gonna go talk to someone.
Hi. is this 3250 Brighton Beach?
Okay. I think I know what that means.
Take off your clothes.
What?
You don't wear clothes in the banya.
Ditch the leotard.
This is not a leotard.
Your text said that this was your office.
This is my office.
Get in.
I'm fine. thanks.
I'll just--
Wah. wah. my office. my rules.
This way. you get to
enjoy a nice. relaxing soak.
and I get to see that
you don't have any weapons.
and we both win.
Okay.
Really?
Would you never take that off?
No. you know. it defeats
the whole anonymous thing.
Even for your girlfriend.
or boyfriend. or whatever?
There's a lot of conjecture online.
And super graphic artwork. have you seen?
The one with you and the ten Mysterios--
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I've seen it.
It's hard to unsee. to be honest.
but look. I don't have anyone.
I just kinda keep to myself.
By yourself all the time?
No wonder you're so sad.
I'm not so sad.
A little bit.
Could we just talk about
what I came here to talk to you
about the attack on damage control?
Yes. so that is more your area.
Like small potato stuff.
Whereas the new Avengers are
focusing on big potato stuff.
Right. okay. well
there's more to it than that.
You know. the driver and
the others who were helping.
it was like someone was
talking to me through them.
Like someone was looking
at me through their eyes.
And you're wondering
if it's mind control.
Exactly.
Like how they used on me in the Red Room.
And the other widows.
Right.
Right. no. I don't think so.
I actually think it's
probably more like possession.
Possession?
Like a ghost or a demon
or in Russia we have Leshy.
Leshy rules the forest and can possess.
Sorry.
Whatever it is. they
are looking for something.
This is the fourth attack
on the damage control
facility this month.
What do you think they're looking for?
I don't know.
But you know what?
After the attack today.
there was a cross
agency cyber security alert
that got triggered.
Someone accessed the damage
control restricted servers
using credentials from 30
employees from the waste station.
They all searched for the same thing.
VMAX.
VMAX?
Well. what does that mean?
I mean. it could be alien tech
or secretive weapon
programs or launch codes or...
I don't know. this is
for you to figure out.
This is small baby potato
stuff. not big potato brain stuff.
You don't have to shout about it. Jeez.
Maybe I'll just go ask
damage control myself.
You know. you're not
completely anonymous anymore.
I have seen your belly button.
Okay. bye.
God.
Hi. I got an appointment with...
Director Metzger. yes.
Please step through the scanner.
Enhanced human detected.
Superior strength.
Superior agility.
Heightened senses.
Exogenous DNA.
Arachnid.
Please remove your face
covering for identity scan.
No. I can't do
that. that's not possible.
Failure to remove your face covering
will result in defensive measures.
Defensive measures. what do you mean?
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
whoa. whoa. guys. guys. guys.
I can't take my mask off.
I'm Spider-Man.
He's all right. at ease.
My apologies.
We are so glad you're here.
Bill Metzger. director of
damage control. how are you?
I'm good. thank you.
We had to beef up security around here.
but I hope we didn't give you a fright.
No. not at all.
All right. come on this way.
This floor is mostly
research and administrative.
Downstairs we have incident cleanup.
laboratories. agent training.
Hey. what are they doing here?
It's okay.
The hand works for us now.
After you brought them in. I
realized that fundamentally
they're a group of kids without a leader.
All they needed was a little direction.
And suddenly all the
things that made them dangerous
turned them into an
invaluable part of our security team.
You can look at the many threats
that face us and see only danger.
or you can see opportunity.
Okay.
Wow. look at that.
In the hands of
Shocker. these are a nuisance.
But it doesn't mean we
can't learn from the technology
or respect the innovation.
Our mission is to
redirect destructive energy
into something useful.
That's the true
meaning of damage control.
Be careful with that.
Right this way.
I wanted to talk to you
about the recent attacks on the agency.
There's been four. right?
Please have a seat.
You are right.
It appears we're faced with
a threat we can't control.
One we can't even see.
But you can.
I saw the security footage.
I also read Detective DeWolf's report.
I believe you understand
exactly what we're up against.
Someone or something that
can hop into people's minds.
But not yours.
No. I mean it tried. but it couldn't.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
We're on our heels right now.
God forbid if we were to get in here
and find whatever it is it's looking for.
the consequences could be unimaginable.
Well let me guess. is
whatever it's looking for
in that giant vault?
There are some things
because of the nature of my job
I cannot tell you.
But I believe you are our
best defense against this.
You're the only one who can sense it.
You're the only one who's immune to it.
I'm counting on you to defeat it.
That's a pretty good speech. Director.
I'll do everything that I can.
I promise.
Well then consider yourself
a friend of damage control.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
I wanted to ask.
The phrase VMAX doesn't
mean anything to you. does it?
No.
Where'd you hear that?
It's just. you know.
nature of being a superhero.
there are some things
I just can't tell you.
Anyway. I'll see you later.
You guys are doing great. keep it up.
I don't think Metzger
knows any more than we do.
but I told him I'd do
whatever I can to help.
You wanna help?
The best thing you
could do is find Scorpion.
He's our only lead.
Yeah. I know.
I have every camera in the city
running a facial
recognition scan for him.
That sounds super illegal. Spider-Man.
I'm gonna pretend I didn't hear that.
Yeah. probably for the best.
But look. if he shows
his face. we'll know.
Do you have any mini-kegs?
Down at the end.
Thanks.
I'll call you back.
Ha.
Easy.
Hey. also. you got any Sharkfire energy?
Yeah.
No. no. no. I don't want any.
That stuff will kill you.
All my friends were
drinking them during the finals
and now they're addicted.
So I'm gonna need you to not sell me any.
Memorize my face.
Please. do not sell
this guy any Sharkfire.
Sure. whatever.
Actually. I'll take one.
Last one.
Maybe two.
And then never sell me any.
Damn it.
Man.
Man. Man.
My guy. appreciate you.
Let's go.
What time did y'all get here?
-We came here. like. half an hour ago.
You need a drink. Take this. take this.
Um. so you've
stumbled across my board.
I'm not one of those weirdos. I swear.
He actually saved me
and my friend's lives
a few times in high school.
Cool.
Yeah. yeah.
And ever since I've just been trying
to figure out who he is.
Not to unmask him to
the world or anything.
just to know. you know?
And then to hopefully
thank him face to face.
I actually created this app
that monitors his sightings.
Where you created Spidey Tracker?
You heard of it. nice.
Where is Spider-Man?
There's a little chat room right there.
Now. we know he's definitely from Queens.
not the biggest revelation.
But I have been able to narrow it down
to two prime suspects.
Yeah. if you knew who they were.
it would really blow your mind.
I'm sure.
Ned. by the way.
I'm. um.
God. there's like 50
people in our apartment.
Statistically speaking.
that means at least two of them
are sociopaths. which is kind of cool.
Nice flowers.
They're a housewarming gift.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
Most people just brought beer and chips.
It's very nice.
I'm MJ.
I'm a. I'm a Maynard.
A Maynard.
You two don't know each other?
No. I'm a neighbor.
A friendly neighbor?
Sorry.
So. how was the interview?
I'm gonna go put these in water.
It was nice to meet you. Maynard.
Nerd. Maynard.
Yeah.
Did you go?
Please tell me that you went.
Yeah. no. I went.
And?
And I got the job.
My God. MJ. that's amazing.
I turned it down.
What?
Yeah. I don't wanna work for some
soulless corporation.
They're not all soulless.
Okay. they're all mostly soulless.
But don't you want
like. health insurance?
Yeah. of course I do. but what costs?
Depends on your deductible.
You mean like your principles.
Yes.
Sorry.
I don't know. I know
it sounds cheesy. but
something is just telling
me that I'm supposed to be
waiting for something.
Great. you know?
Okay.
To waiting for something great.
Waiting for something great.
Well. the wait is over.
Your new home.
Dude. this is top shelf.
Just like you.
I wanna hide this.
I lifted this off of him again.
But what if Ned needs the
fire of a thousand sharks?
You mean heart palpitation.
You can't save everyone.
I can try.
That's my girl.
I'm sorry.
I got it.
When we get into MIT.
we should live together.
Yeah. for sure.
Yeah. I love that.
Be a fresh start and
we'll all be together.
Yeah. no. you're right.
Yeah. fresh start.
You're gonna forget who I am.
Okay. what are you talking about?
It's okay.
I'm gonna come and find you
and I'll explain everything.
I'm gonna just wait.
Wait. tell me.
Can you see me again?
My name is Peter
Parker and I like a coffee.
Is there anything else?
No.
Hey.
They think you don't have to listen to me
now that you've got powers.
You know. this whole
thing can get really scary.
You know that?
Well yeah. it's already pretty scary.
Yeah. and things can change very quickly.
Ways that we can't
even imagine right now.
Believe me. I know.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
What?
I live here. I just. um.
I'm gonna grab my stuff.
Is that my shirt?
No. Cute dog.
Shh.
Hi Peter. you have 107 new alerts.
Please check backlog.
What is happening?
The results of your
body scan show a surge
in the hormones
associated with your arachnid DNA.
resulting in the formation
of organic web spinnerets
and dangerously
heightened sensory receptors.
Okay. but I feel fine.
Prolonged isolation or emotional trauma
could be contributing
to this sudden change.
Have you experienced any
recent traumatic events?
Peter?
I'm fine. E.V..
You don't seem fine.
I recommend you take
some time to rebalance.
Well. that's not really an option. is it?
Mechanical web shooters and organic webs
cannot be used simultaneously.
Come on. Peter.
Alert. senses are overloaded.
What the hell was that?
Your heightened senses are taking in
too much information at once.
Okay. it's okay. it's okay.
All right. organic webs.
Peter Two had 'em. He was cool.
You're cool.
My God. that's hideous.
Okay. here we go.
Okay. that didn't work.
Organic webs. come on. and bam.
Stop.
What's going on. E.V.?
Shots fired at the
Damage Control Data Center
in Manhattan.
Suspect facial match with Scorpion.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Come on. three. two. one.
Web stop.
Birds. birds. birds!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Web stop.
God.
Web stop stop stop.
I don't know what you're looking for.
I'm looking for V-Max.
I don't know anything.
I'll see for myself.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I've had a really crazy day.
Scorpion. do we really
gotta keep doing this?
My head is killing me.
You think I'm Scorpion?
Web stop.
What's happening to you?
You can't sense me anymore.
You. what's going on with you Spider-Man?
Warning. arachnid hormones increasing.
Who are you?
Do you know who you are?
We need some help over here.
Come on. come and go.
Spider-Man.
What the hell?
Somebody get a medic.
DeWolff. is she hurt?
Is she okay?
No. Just let me go.
What is going on over there?
That wasn't Scorpion. okay?
I mean. it was. but he
was possessed by whatever.
Hijacked that tank. okay?
Look. please. can I just--
Slow down.
Listen. I don't know what this is.
but I need you to pull it together.
You almost killed a cop.
This isn't you.
I know. I'm sorry.
If you act like this
again. I cannot protect you.
Whatever this is. you need to fix it.
Through lattice chromodynamics.
we can arrange time and space in a grid.
which allows us to simulate
the quarks binding into the protons.
Cindy. is this a question about protons
or more stuff about Avengers?
Okay.
I love to tell stories. but you know.
I gotta teach you some
physics at some point. yeah.
All right. let it rip. Cindy.
If Thanos was so
worried about overpopulation.
why didn't he just use the
magic glove to make more food?
Arthur. you wanna answer that question?
Hulk!
Hi. Tyler.
Excuse me. Dr. Banner?
You okay?
Yeah. sorry. it's just a headache.
Have you got a minute?
I wanted to talk to
you about your inhibitor.
Sure.
Don't worry. it's got failsafe.
so I'm not gonna turn into
the big green raging monster
machine in the cafeteria.
But if you do see me
let this thing off. run.
No. but you're using
target specific short
and a fearing RNA. right?
It's like gene silencing.
you're just incorporating
the gamma radiation.
What'd you say your name was?
Ned. please.
So you found a way to
suppress the expression of DNA.
even as it's undergoing the mutation
due to gamma radiation. right?
Yes.
Okay. so my question
is. would that same thing
be possible with DNA that's
mutating for another reason?
What's the reason?
I don't know.
Let's say that the host genome is mixed
with some kind of
foreign DNA. theoretically.
Theoretically. yes. it's possible. yes.
So could you suppress only some parts
of that DNA expression?
Like the bad aspects. but
just keep all the good stuff?
You mean like if I
wanted to keep some parts
of Hulk but not others?
Right.
It would be enormously
dangerous and complex.
but if you were able to target the
correct mRNA strand.
possibly.
Wait. so you could just
turn the mutating gene
on and off as long as you do it
before the mRNA transcription?
Maybe.
I mean. if you apply the same thinking.
you could even develop some
kind of automatic inhibitor
that would just adjust
to any type of mutation.
Well. now you're talking
about a universal inhibitor
that would control
anyone who has any powers.
It's a dangerous idea.
Well. yeah. but it's theoretical. right?
You're not one of my students. are you?
No. I'm a grad student.
I've taken enough of your time.
I gotta get some
books back to the library.
The library's that way.
Right. right.
How would you decide?
What's that?
Well. what parts of
nature are good or bad?
What if you're trying
to control the expression
of something that needs to be expressed?
Good luck with your studies. Ned.
Thank you. Professor.
Like reptiles.
amphibians. and arthropods.
spiders shed skin at key
points at their life cycles.
The process is known as molting.
Fourth inhibitor prototype complete.
While loading is a part
of the spider's lifecycle.
it can leave the
spider vulnerable for a--
Upload inhibitor beta build seven.
Uploaded. would you like to run a test?
Yeah. run it.
Spiders have three
stages in their lifecycle.
Each stage is
characterized by physical changes
with the largest changes occurring
during the beautiful
transition to adulthood.
For those who make it through.
moting amounts to a kind of beeper--
Can you turn that spider stuff off?
Turning off video.
Inhibitor active.
Here we are. come on. come on.
Keep an eye on my vitals.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing arachnid
hormones to your baseline levels.
Okay.
All right. E.V.. let's do this.
Initiating field test one.
That's working.
Alert. inhibitor is overheating.
Functionality reducing.
Yeah. I'm sensing that.
Alert. senses are overloaded.
Alert. senses. senses. senses.
alert. over alert.
Web grenades activated.
Shit.
Inhibitor field test one. failure.
Yo. Spider-Man.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm just trying out some new tech.
Yeah.
To get rid of that monster inside you?
Still can't sense me?
Guess your technology isn't working.
You know. you're the only person I met
that I can't hop into.
I'm sure that's
really frustrating for you.
Well. I'll get in there one day.
What do you want?
Well. I know why a
half-human. half-Spider
would decide to work for an organization
whose sworn mission is to hunt down
anybody who's different.
Damage Control isn't after you
because you're different.
They're hunting you down
because you're dangerous.
Now. what do you want?
Since you're a very simple Spider.
let me spell it out for you.
Damage control has something that I need.
You mean V-Max?
I was planning to use Scorpion to get it.
but you keep getting in my way.
I will always be in your way.
You sure about that. Peter Parker?
You know. your apartment
is kind of like a parody
of where you think a sad
single guy in his 20s might live.
Takeout containers. free
weights. protein powder.
You're bluffing.
You know. it ain't all
hard to track down. Peter.
Well. that beats not for someone like me.
I did find one interesting thing. though.
And of all places. coffee cup.
EV Display Home Workstation.
You spent four years erasing
Peter Parker from existence?
No wonder the Spider's
trying to swallow up the man.
I wonder if MJ would even recognize you.
I think I might go see how she's doing.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
No. her roommate was nice enough
to post a new address online.
How about this?
I'll race you there.
If you touch her. let her start swinging.
I'm fast.
Hey. it's a long way to MJ's.
You better pick up the pace.
E.V.. track physical anomalies.
Searching for physical
anomalies between subjects.
Please stand by.
Thank you all so much for coming today.
I'm sorry about that.
Give it up for Spider-Man.
In a race for the love of his life.
then it's not looking good.
Come on. Spidey.
Keep up.
Excuse me. sorry.
E.V.. run these numbers with the others.
Analyzing jump distances for patterns.
Give me that cube. Dana!
Calculating.
Come on. I need an answer!
Calculations complete.
You have a limit to
your jump radius. don't ya?
33 feet.
I don't see anybody up
here for you to hop into.
Very clever.
Like I said. you're not getting near her.
Hey. hey. hey. hey!
I'm sorry. but you're in danger.
Where's your roommate?
What?
Where's Nick?
I bossed him with friends. why?
Okay. good.
You got a couple of me.
But I don't know if
you're the real Spider-Man
or not coming with you.
We don't have time for
this. please come on.
You need to get out of my apartment!
Look. this is gonna sound insane.
but there is someone who is after you
who is really dangerous. okay?
And I promised you that
I would keep you safe.
Please. you just have
to trust me. come on.
Fine.
Where would you stop?
Are you okay?
Yeah. yeah. I'm fine.
Okay. well. we should be safe up here.
Okay. we'll see from what?
I'm not entirely sure.
Okay. well. what do they want with me?
I don't know.
You don't know?
It doesn't make any sense.
why would they choose me?
Um. I wish I could
tell you. I just...
We knew each other. didn't we?
What?
It's the only explanation.
It's been driving me crazy for years.
all the times that
Spider-Man saved either me or Ned.
It was the Washington Monument.
and then it was London. and
Prague. and the Night Monkey.
I mean. twice as a
coincidence. but over and over again.
We knew each other. tell me I'm wrong.
You're wrong.
What were we. were we classmates. or
friends. or something?
Like. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Were we something more?
I just. I can't. I can't remember.
and I feel like
someone scrambled my brain.
and you're the only
one who would know why.
This is crazy. and I can't--
I know that you can't tell me the truth.
but I need to know.
Maybe there's a part of
me that still remembers.
Peter?
-MJ?
Hey.
I've missed you so much.
I can't believe you figured it out.
I did.
Go ahead. Peter.
Touch her.
Hold her.
You've been wanting to for so long.
True love's kiss breaks the spell.
and reunites the star-crossed lovers.
MJ would vomit.
You really are a
simple spider. aren't you?
I see why you like her.
She's. she's smart.
Funny.
A little dark and twisted.
I mean. it is sad.
There is. like. no
thoughts of you in here.
whatsoever.
But you knew that. didn't you?
You're a monster.
If you loved someone
the way that I love her.
then you'd know that
what you're doing right now
is unforgivable.
Is that so?
You know. some people would kill
to hold the person
they loved one last time.
Stop it now.
You're running out of time. Peter.
Soon enough. it won't
just be your friends
who don't remember Peter Parker.
Maybe you should write
a letter to yourself.
Get out of her.
Who's the monster now. Peter?
Okay. okay. no. no. no.
God. God. please. no. come on.
Come on. come on. come on.
Thank God. thank God.
You're okay. you're okay.
I'm so sorry.
Stop. will we stop. stop. please?
Quit. you win. you win.
you win. just don't hurt her.
You're a mess. Spider-Man.
Any time I want.
I can be anyone I want.
So you can't protect
MJ. even from herself.
It really is a nice
letter. little heavy-handed.
Not bad.
You're okay. I'm gonna
take you someplace safe.
Take me to 3165.
Lafayette Street.
Navigating to Empire State University.
I got you. I got you.
You sure?
Yep.
Okay. because I feel like
I'm slipping a little bit.
You're not slipping.
Okay.
You're okay. you're okay.
you're okay. you're okay.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Okay. can we just slow down
for like two seconds. please?
We're almost there.
Yeah. but you just told
me I was mind-controlled.
Well. not technically.
And you're lucky I
believe in that stuff. okay?
Because governments have
been doing it for years.
especially the French.
Are you okay?
Yeah. look. sorry.
I'm just trying to take
you someplace safe. okay?
I don't feel safe.
Shit.
Sorry.
Watch Out!
You're losing it. kid.
Thought you'd be able to
see that coming a mile away.
What is wrong with you?
You could have killed us.
Excuse me?
You show up to my house.
and then ask what do
you think's gonna happen?
Wait. this is your house?
No. no. don't.
Who the hell is that?
What the hell are you?
She's. um. you know.
No. I don't know.
that's why I just asked you.
She's in danger. Frank.
Look. I need your help. okay?
Yeah. it looks like it.
Come on. you owe me.
Fuck.
Aren't you sick of this story?
Staten Island.
Nah. Staten Island.
What more do you want me to do?
I literally saved your life.
You're out of your mind. kid!
I gotta save it twice to get a favor?
That guy could'nt hit me
with a handful of rice.
What does that sound like to you?
-A drug dealer was gonna shoot a guy...
I had him exactly where I want him.
I'm seein' him right there.
- ...then I webbed the gun...
...out of the drug dealer's hand...
-I know exactly what I'm...
...completely up for.
-...and then kicked that drug dealer...
-Okay. fine. go ahead.
-...back into a storage container.
What does that sound like to you?
I don't care. I just wanna go home.
That's an excellent idea.
Kick rocks. go home.
No. no. wait. wait. wait. wait.
Frank. Frank. Frank. Frank. wait. please.
Hey. I've got to keep her safe. okay?
And I don't have anywhere else to go.
You like chili?
I made chili.
All right. just watch
out for the claymores.
I wanna pick up pieces at
you for the next two weeks.
Hey. I definitely
would not eat that chili.
So you're telling me that maniac
behind all that tank nonsense?
Nothing but a goddamn teenager.
And it's not just a
tank. it's every attack
on damage control this past month.
How does a kid learn how to drive a tank?
I don't know. Frank.
Beat your ass all over
the street like that.
She did not beat my ass.
Is this your family?
She'll get the hell away from that.
Look. I got one rule in this house.
You don't touch anything.
you don't move anything.
you sure as shit don't
ask me any goddamn questions
about anything.
So three rules.
I see why you like her.
Go put some pants on.
Don't touch the chili.
I like him.
Of course you do.
So I managed to pull
this image from my HUD
and run it through the system.
Who is she?
Until a couple months ago. nobody.
She was in and out of
foster care. psych hospitals.
and then eventually she ran away and
dropped off the grid.
It's hardly any information about her
that hasn't been scrubbed.
but she's classified as a telepath.
and now we have a name.
Jean Grey.
Yeah. these are the damage control sites
that she hasn't hit yet.
So if she surfaces. then
my facial tracking program
will pick her up.
Right.
Yeah. more then.
Well. don't worry about what then.
Just look after her.
Don't worry about it?
I'm just supposed to sit here
and babysit your girlfriend.
She's not my girlfriend.
All right. look. what's the plan?
Just gotta hope that your
facial tracking program works.
You get yourself killed.
I gotta watch her the rest of my life.
I'm not gonna get killed. Frank.
I can catch her. okay?
I just have to fix my
inhibitor and then I'll be good to go.
What do you need to do that?
Frank. you do not have
what I need to do that. okay?
You've got some mouth on you.
What. do you think you
have an anti-static mat.
a tonal probe and micro tools?
I got all that shit.
What for?
Bombs.
Bingo.
Unbelievable.
Hey. do you think it's safe to maybe call someone
and let them know I'm okay?
Like your boyfriend?
No. like my roommate.
Um. I don't think that's
such a good idea. you know.
because she already knows who he is
and she can inhabit anyone she wants.
Right. yeah.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah. you're right.
Sorry.
No. it's fine. I totally get it.
If I called my boyfriend.
he'd just ask me a bunch of questions
that I couldn't answer and he'd tell me
I was being withholding again.
Withholding?
Yep.
Sounds like your
boyfriend's kind of a jerk.
Why do you think you're withholding?
I don't know. he'd tell me
mass vigilante behind the curtain.
Okay. I see your point. Um. okay. I see your point.
So what about you?
What about me?
Well. do you have Mrs. Spider-Man?
Do I have Mrs. Spider-Man?
Um.
no. no.
Why not?
Because I'm too withholding. obviously.
Welcome to the club.
There was someone.
Really?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
What happened?
I.
I had to let her go.
To keep her safe.
I'm sorry. that must have
been really hard for you.
Yeah. it was. yeah.
It is.
It is really hard.
Are you okay?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I'm okay.
I. go ahead.
You know what. it's gonna come over--
Hold on. hold on. hold
on. hold on. hold on.
What's going on?
Um. it just keeps overheating on me.
It's been stumping me for days.
Before I switched to aerospace.
I was gonna major in
biochemical engineering. so.
Do you mind if I--
Yeah. for sure. here.
There you go.
Wow.
So. does the device itself.
I mean. does it
generate any kind of radiation
or a magnetic field?
Cause that would definitely interfere.
Yeah. it has a micro magnetic field.
but I accounted for that in the design.
Okay. well. what about your suit?
It actually
dissipates into the fabric.
which is pretty cool.
Okay.
What about those?
What about what?
Your goggles. or whatever you call them.
They would create a
field. it would be tiny. but--
But it's on your head.
which is very close to the inhibitor.
Which is probably why it's overheating.
MJ. that is genius.
Okay. this has to work.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing selected arachnid hormones.
Okay. that feels better.
That feels totally better.
My head feels so clear.
And I'm not shooting organic webs.
My God. MJ. that like totally worked.
You know. this is
some really intense stuff
you're working on here.
Well. yeah. it's really important.
Yeah. but this is like.
I mean. this is like altering your DNA.
I mean. this is the
kind of stuff you put on.
like. I don't know. like a monster.
Well. if you see
what's been happening to me
over the last couple of days.
then you might understand.
Yeah. well. I've been with
you for the last few hours.
and that's not what I've seen.
And what have you seen?
From my side of the curtain?
A really good guy.
I might just be changing.
I don't mean to overstep.
I'll let you get back to it.
Can't sleep either?
You want coffee?
Sure.
You get your shit fixed.
Yeah. I've been wearing it all night.
So far. so good.
I made this other one universal.
So if I could get it on Jean.
it should completely
shut down her powers.
You know what else would work?
You just shoot her.
Nice.
Jesus Christ.
That's gotta be the goofiest shit
I've ever seen in my life.
But you can't even take the mask off.
Drink a cup of coffee.
Don't take it personally. Frank.
It stays on for everybody.
Even her?
Who is she. kid?
I don't know.
That's horseshit.
Who is she?
I'm telling you. I don't know who she is.
You care about her.
You're pretending not to lie.
I don't care about her.
Look. I don't know
who she is. Frank. okay?
I don't have anybody.
I'm like you.
I just keep to myself.
You're like me.
What do you know about me. kid?
You think this is a choice?
Living like this?
It's a lifestyle?
Is that what you think?
Kid. this is a sentence.
If I had one second.
people I love are still breathing.
You think I'd be hiding behind a mask?
You think I'd pretend to
be something that I'm not?
Acting like a goddamn coward?
I got a facial match.
She's at the Damage
Control HQ in Manhattan.
I gotta go.
I'm okay.
She's gonna be okay.
I'll see to it.
Thanks. Frank.
Hey.
You just gonna let him go by himself?
You know. I think he might need you.
Hey.
Kinda like you needed
him on Staten Island.
You can't hide from me forever. Bill.
You've got a strong door.
but it's the wall you
have to worry about.
Who are you and what do you want?
I'm Jean Grey.
And you know what I want.
Jean?
You looked me up.
I'm blushing.
I told you what would happen to your girl
if you got in my way.
You're not getting near her again.
And you're definitely not
getting inside that vault.
Maybe not.
But this guy might.
Jean. you don't know
what you're dealing with.
You know. you and
Banner have a lot in common.
Both fighting the losing battle
against the monster
that lives inside you.
Jean. this is the Hulk you can't destroy.
What the hell?
I see.
Trying to muzzle me
like you muzzle yourself?
I can't let you in there.
Whatever V-Max is. you're not getting it.
Like hell I'm not.
Jean. don't do this.
Save your breath.
Frank. what are you doing here?
I think I'm doing it.
I'm saving your ass.
This is way above your pay grade.
You're fighting the Hulk.
Shit.
Really?
Get out!
Stop shooting him!
Are you out of your goddamn mind?
Banner's not the problem! She is.
I thought I told you to
stay home and watch MJ.
Yeah. you did.
And then she tells me
I gotta come watch you.
Wait. did she actually say that to you?
Are you blushing. daffodil?
Blushing?
God damn it. I knew I
should have brought a bigger gun.
That's a good idea. bring a bigger gun.
What are you gonna
do. tickle him to death?
No. look. change your plan.
First we get this on the
Hulk. then we go after Jean.
I got one better.
That's the highest
casualty producing threat.
You contain it. I go find
the source. I take it down.
You got it?
Are you just trying to get
out of fighting the Hulk?
I guess so.
Okay. whatever dude. I got this.
No. Frank. Frank. Frank. Frank!
What?
Do not kill her!
Don't start with that
soft serve bullshit .
You know something. I'm gonna do this.
I'm gonna do it my way. just go. just go.
Don't get within 33 feet!
Yeah.
So frustrating.
Hey.
Whoa.
This guy's got issues.
No. no. not again.
No.
Dr. Banner. is that you?
Spider-Man. what happened?
Where am I?
Hey. hey. hey.
Did I do all this?
Did I hurt anyone?
It's not your fault.
she was in your mind.
You weren't in control.
I lost my inhibiting.
Look. here. here.
It's the only thing
keeping the monster inside.
It's okay. I got another one.
I just need you to put this on.
What is it?
It's universal. it should work on you.
Please sir. there's
people in the building.
just put it on.
You okay?
It's my head.
I think she broke something.
Is she still in there?
No. it's the other guy.
Bruce?
Look. I could get you out of here. okay?
I just need you to put that inhibitor on.
Get away from me!
I can't control.
Yes you can. Bruce.
Yes you can.
Get out of the building.
Get everyone out of the floor.
Banner. please. look at me.
No Banner. no girl.
I didn't know you could get that big.
Whoa.
Good luck with that. Peter.
There you are.
Just hold still. just hold still.
Okay.
No lethal rounds.
Tracking time to detonation.
90 seconds to detonation.
I know. I know.
Why is your skin so thick?
The inhibitor cannot attach.
No. come on.
Dr. Banner.
Please.
Bruce. it's Peter.
I'm your friend.
Bruce!
Throw down your guns or you'll get the
next one in the head.
Where is she?
Why did she?
It's over. Jean.
Sarah.
Sell my gun.
Is anyone hurt?
Is it just me?
Spider-Man.
You saved my life.
And you saved God knows how many lives
by making sure she didn't find
what she was looking for in there.
Before she passed out.
she tried to say something.
A name. Sarah.
Does that mean something to you?
Before you got the inhibitor on her.
she managed to get in
my mind for a moment.
Sarah was the name of
someone I worked closely with
that recently passed.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Somehow the memory of
Sarah must have affected her.
Well. I'd love to talk
to her when she wakes up.
but of course. she'll be
transferred to our facility
on Roosevelt Island.
Now. I'm just as eager to
get her talking as you are.
but let's not strain
her too much in one day.
Yeah. of course.
Thank you. Spider-Man.
My pleasure.
Okay. it worked.
She's in custody.
You're safe now.
You left this?
No. no. um. look. I can explain. okay?
Can you take that off. please?
What?
The mask.
I think I deserve to
have this conversation
with Peter Parker.
He came to the party at our
apartment the other night.
In the donut shop.
The year I went off to school.
Why didn't you tell me then?
I was trying to protect you.
I've almost been
killed like five times
the past 24 hours. so it's
not really working that well.
I know. I'm sorry.
Were you ever gonna tell me?
Right?
So you just were gonna
make that decision for me.
I know. I'm sorry.
I don't really need you to
keep saying that. you're sorry.
I don't know what you
want me to tell you.
I want you to tell me why
you would do this to me.
I lost someone.
And they'd still be
here if it wasn't for me.
I didn't read you that letter because
I didn't want anything
like that to happen to you.
That's not really your decision.
I know it's not. but
you mean everything to me.
And I've been trying to live
my life without you. but I.
I can't.
I love you.
This spell. or
whatever it is that you did.
it worked.
All these memories that you're saying
that we have together.
I don't.
I don't have them.
And I do see why. you
know. she would love you.
the girl you wrote that letter to.
but
I understand that you did what
you had to do to protect her.
And for that. I'm so grateful.
But I.
I don't love you.
You said I don't. I don't even know you.
I should probably go now.
I really am sorry. Peter.
I don't have a phone.
Come.
Do you mind taking me home?
Yeah. of course.
Thank you.
Yeah. sure.
I'm gonna.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. of course.
Do you wanna come up?
Just to say hi to Ned. maybe?
I would love that.
The Hulk. AKA Dr. Bruce
Banner. is in custody.
currently being
transferred to a psychiatric ward.
So sad.
After years as a peaceful academic.
the question the world asks today is.
what finally snapped?
Hey. I'm nearby.
MJ? Yeah.
You're not gonna believe this.
but the Spidey Tracker
app says that Spider-Man
is in the direct vicinity.
Yeah. no way. that's crazy.
Hey. I'm nearby.
Ned. Spider-Man. Spider-Man. Ned.
It's nice to meet you. Ned.
Hello.
I'm not like a weirdo or anything.
He's a little weird.
Why. why are you here?
I--
I was on the subway.
Platform. right. and
she was on her phone.
Yeah. I got a little distracted.
and the train was coming.
And I just swooped her right up.
Yeah. saved it. man.
My God.
Why has that never happened to me?
So what if you're mid-swing.
and you decide you need to pee?
Do you just land on top of a building?
What?
Do you drop down the ground level
and run into a coffee
shop. and you're like.
"Hey. Spider-Man. I need to pee."
Or do you find a rooftop somewhere?
No. I don't find a
rooftop somewhere. Ned.
Is this really what you want
to be asking him right now?
Yeah. dude. come on.
You can ask me anything.
You want to know how
my web shooters work?
I mean. I already know
how the web shooters work.
Is that right?
Well. there's obviously some sort of
sheer thinning fluid
that is cycling within a chamber. right?
So it can keep its liquid form.
And then when you activate it
by pressing all the triggers.
it runs through a Teflon turbine.
and then it hardens when it interacts
with the air. right?
I mean. not exactly. but...
Okay. okay. well then tell
me what's in the web fluid.
I guess something like
a long-chain polymer.
Nylon?
That's pretty close.
Okay. okay.
What about Nomex or...
Kevlar!
All right. then keep your secrets.
If you were referring to
the incident with the dragon.
I was barely involved.
All I did was simply give your uncle
a little nudge out the door.
Solid reference.
Ooh. Banh mi time!
You ordered Banh mi?
I ordered five Banh mis.
I've Spider-Man in the apartment. he's gonna get fed.
Sorry about him.
He's just. like. very
excited that you're here.
Are you kidding?
This is. like. the most
fun I've had in years.
I really miss you guys.
You guys really do
look like best friends.
What do you mean?
You should tell him.
He can handle it.
Yeah. I know.
Um...
When she was
inhabiting you on the rooftop.
she kissed me.
and I kissed her back.
Because I thought it was
you. but I didn't know.
And I'm really sorry.
I just thought you should know.
Thanks for telling me.
I mean. it's not like I
remember anything anyway. so...
Really?
Yeah. it was weird. It was like one
second I was sitting at my desk.
and the next second I
was lying on the street.
I don't know. like a
light switch went off.
What?
So you don't remember anything?
No. why?
Metzger said he remembered thinking about
someone named Sarah.
but what you're saying is that you don't
remember anything at all.
I mean. yeah. it was instantaneous.
That's what made it so scary.
He lied to me.
I heard you called Leshy.
Yeah. her name's Jean Grey. I need some
help determining the
size of some potatoes.
Potatoes?
I think that's back with Al.
I think Metzger lied
to me about her name.
Can you see if there's a connection
between Jean and someone named Sarah?
These potatoes sound meager.
Well. that really is your office.
Well. well. well.
Internet. government records.
and a lot of data related to Jean Grey
has been scrubbed by damage control.
Data about what?
Her sister.
Wait. Jean has a sister?
Sarah Grey.
Also a telepath?
Damage control to current custody for
study and observation.
Wow. I mean. you can probably
guess what they mean by that.
Experimentation and other
human rights violations?
Yes. exactly. Wait. who are you?
Hi. Ned Leeds. big fan.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
I'm just so happy that
this sad man has friends.
Thanks. I owe you one.
Good luck. Spider-Man.
Bye. She was just looking for her sister.
and I handed her to
the people that took her.
I gotta go.
Hey. Peter?
Yeah.
You should be careful. right?
Yeah. I will.
Spider-Man's name is Peter?
Jean. who do you want to be?
Her. Pink jacket.
She's too far.
You're gonna have to hop.
Hop?
First. pick someone close.
And then...
The hop has a limit. but you can string
them together and go as far as you want.
And when you let go...
You're right back where you started.
Could you do that to
everyone in this park at once?
Yeah. maybe one day.
If you get really good.
Now could she just...
send us away?
She wasn't really a mom.
Not like that anyway.
She was. Before we changed.
Yeah. well. if that's all it takes for
you to stop being a mom.
you're gonna have to be a redhead.
Shut up.
We have each other.
You know. we have ice cream.
One mint chip. one chocolate?
Yeah.
Okay.
Don't fall.
Get down! Get down! Get down!
Sarah!
I'm sorry. Jean.
I have to keep you safe.
Subject is awake. Heart rate is 94 BPM.
Jean. that's not gonna work anymore.
Thanks to Spider-Man.
Jean?
I need you to breathe.
I need you to look at me and breathe.
Okay? You're safe.
Breathe.
Where is she?
Like your sister. you've been blessed
with a power that has the potential to do
tremendous good in the world.
or tremendous damage.
A power like yours in the hands of a
child is an impossible burden.
But imagine
if that power was placed in the hands of
people who actually
know what to do with it.
Where is my sister?
You're gonna change the world. Jean.
Hey! Hey! No! Frank? I know where you
are. what you're doing.
Yeah. and how's that?
Got eyes everywhere. kid.
Look. Frank. damage control kidnapped
Jean's sister. Jean was just trying to
find her. We were wrong about everything.
Sentimental horse shit.
You've seen what she can do and what
she's capable of. What. you gonna let her
loose? Is that what you're gonna do?
I'll tell you right now. you do that.
I handle it my way.
Frank. please. you're doing it. Frank!
The distance check.
40 foot clearance.
Locking down the room.
Locking down.
Disengage inhibitor.
Jean. your powers are
now fully operational.
As you can tell. we are
beyond your jump radius.
Tell me what VMAX is.
You're the second person to ask me about
that. I have no idea what that means.
She sent me a message. She
was trying to help me find her.
She communicated with you telepathically
across all that distance.
We did register a huge
spike in that session.
Fascinating.
What does it mean. asshole?
I don't know. Let's begin.
I work with Sarah centered on two areas.
Identifying the source of her power and
identifying a path towards copying it.
If we could find a way to record a
telepathic brain during a jump. then
perhaps we could replicate those pathways
in the mind of our choosing.
This instrument is your sister's legacy.
We built this together over
many months of trial and error.
I hope you and I can honor her sacrifice.
What are you talking about?
Trigger the first jump.
Tell me what VMAX is. I know
that's where you're hiding her.
She's jumping.
Copy. We're in full
lockdown. Process has commenced.
What process?
Hey. whoa. that's a pretty
serious look there. dude.
Hey. whoa. what the hell. man? Come on.
I'm a friend of Damage
Control. What are you doing?
It's gonna be
like that. You wanna go.
All right. All right. Just
give me a sec. Give me a sec.
I'm not in high school anymore.
Did you stretch you big stretcher? I
mean. you should do in your line of work.
What about you? You guys
stretch? It's so good for you.
You ready?
Watch your head.
Where is Jean Grey?
Let's jump 26. Recordings look good.
Excuse me. sir. We have an intruder.
You were right. She's
much stronger than her sister.
Increase the frequency.
You're doing very well. Jean.
Jean?
Jean. can you hear me?
You're a murderer.
Her frequencies are
evolving. This doesn't make sense.
The last thing my
sister saw was this room.
The brainwaves are somehow
affecting the objects around her.
Shut it down.
I'm trying. sir.
What do you mean you're trying?
The last thing my sister
saw was this goddamn room.
Shut it down. I can't. sir.
Move.
I can't let you do that. Bill.
The only hands that will
wield this power are mine.
What do you want?
Jean. I'm here to help you.
You put me here.
I know. and I'm sorry about Sarah. and
I'm sorry that I got it so wrong.
I'm sorry. If you came here to save a helpless girl
from damage control. you're too late.
They're the ones who need saving.
And now. so do you.
Here we go.
God. that's cool.
Fuck!
Jean!
Jean. please!
Come on! Come on. come on!
What the...
Isn't it funny how your friends from
damage control developed a
special weapon just for you?
They've got a whole task force ready.
just in case you ever get out of line.
People are monsters.
You shouldn't trust them
any more than they trust you.
I'm a little busy. Frank.
We got a problem. kid.
She got ahold of everyone within a
kilometer of the island.
Wait. what?
Look. if you're gonna do
something. you better do it now.
I'm trying!
Kid!
Shit!
My sister died in this
room. surrounded by these men.
And her only crime was that she was
special. just like you.
Just like me.
People like us don't
get to live a normal life.
We don't get to have friends or a family.
Those people are gone.
That life is over.
So why don't you just
be honest with yourself?
Are you Peter Parker?
Or are you Spider-Man?
I'm both.
Hey. move!
No!
Jean. please.
This won't make it right.
Come on. you're not a killer. Jean.
You have no idea what I am.
I know that you loved your sister.
And I know that losing her
felt like he'd lost everything.
If you come any
closer. he dies! They all do!
You know this won't
bring her back. right. Jean?
Don't be so sure I
can't get into your mind.
I'm a lot more
powerful since I last tried.
Go ahead.
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen to me
now that I've got powers?
You know. this whole
thing would get really scary.
You know that?
It's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change very quickly.
Ways that we can't
even imagine right now.
I know.
No.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
You're a really special person.
And I would hope that that will always
make you feel really
great about yourself.
But I know sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes you'll be really lonely.
And sometimes. because you're special.
people can do dark.
monstrous things to you.
But. this is what I want you to know.
You're beautiful. and the
people who love you. we love you.
Not because you're special.
we love you because you're you.
I want you to remember that.
Even when it feels
like you're totally alone.
That's your deepest responsibility.
Never forget that no
matter how powerful you become.
Hey.
I'm sorry about your sister.
I'm sorry about your aunt.
Yeah. you would have loved her.
Just because we've lost someone.
it doesn't mean we have to do this alone.
I mean. we can't.
Trust me. I've been trying.
It doesn't work.
Even if that's true.
I have no one.
You have me?
You hurt?
Fine.
I'm okay.
Peter.
I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Peter. Peter.
No. no. no. no. no. no. Peter.
You gotta get out of here.
They'll be looking for you.
No. no. no. no. no. no.
Please just stay with me.
Come on. hold on. come on. please.
You're gonna be okay.
Just go.
Get up.
Look at me.
Shock today.
A Spider-Man arrived at Bellevue Hospital
with a bullet wound.
seemingly at death's door.
The reclusive crime
fighter is in critical condition
as the city's top medical
experts work to save him.
Tonight. all eyes are on Spider-Man.
The hero who saved New York so many times
is now in the hands of
its best and brightest.
And the people of New
York hold their breath.
Frank?
Where am I?
No. no. no. no. no. no. no. hey.
Where's my mask?
Don't worry about that. I got you covered.
You good?
Where's Jean. is she okay?
Yeah. she's okay.
She's okay.
Where is she?
I think maybe she just left.
She was using her magic
voodoo shit to keep you alive.
Yeah. she's all right.
I'm sorry.
Frank.
Just. I'm really sorry for what I did.
No. Frank. it's okay.
I know it's a lot of things.
but it sure shit ain't okay. all right?
I seen. I seen real bravery.
I'm sorry.
Kid. my day.
Put that down.
That was something else.
You crying?
No. I ain't crying.
You know. you looked the
exact way I thought you would.
You're a nice kid.
Never had a friend like that.
Are we friends now?
I can't believe I just saw you cry.
Cry. what are you talking about?
Bullshit.
Yeah. they've
been doing it all night.
Been here since you walked in.
Let's take a look.
Yo. kid. when you came in. they had to
cut through the suit.
but when you're ready
to split. I got a plan.
Hey. it's Spider-Man!
Spider-Man!
You're the best. Spider-Man!
Over here!
We love you!
I've. been thinking a
lot about what you said.
and you'd be happy to know
that I've decided I'm not.
I'm not gonna do this alone anymore.
I miss you. May.
I mean. I've still got a
little pain in my back.
but I could probably get back out there
if you need me for anything.
What I need you to do is rest.
I know. I know. but come on.
you gotta give me something.
I mean. how's the investigation going?
Well. Metzger's still missing.
What. your friend. Black Widow.
she's been helping us
dig through all the records
damage control tried to have scrubbed.
Had me dropped by her
office the other day?
And how was that?
Well. my skin feels amazing.
Attention all units.
we have a confirmed
bank robbery in progress.
Hey. are you getting this?
Yeah. I'm on it.
Hey. it's not that far from me.
I could probably meet you down there.
No. we can handle a robbery.
Just try to take care of yourself.
Okay.
You too.
Say hello to E.J. Marley for me.
Okay.
Spider-Man says hello.
Hi.
Hey.
Flower guy. right?
From the party?
I'm Peter.
Okay. hello.
Peter.
New Spider-Man
sighting. Location unknown.
Location unknown. Location unknown.
Location found.
SPIDER-MAN will be back.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org